Officer He.
Honey. One mutton rice noodle.
-Extra coriander.
-Alright.
To go. Make it fast.
Officer He. We haven't seen you in ages.
The criminal department
is busier than the station?
I'll be back in three days.
That's good. That's good.
We're all eager to have you back.
Officer He.
There's a newcomer at the station.
Officer… Officer Qu.
We've never seen him smile.
Difficult person.
Tell everyone to be at ease.
Once I'm back,
I'll get that poker face out of here.
Wait. One more noodle. No coriander.
Alright. One more noodle. No coriander.
-Alright.
-I'm on it.
POLICE CODE OF CONDUCT
ON UNIFORM AND APPEARANCE
I haven't slept for days.
CONFERENCE ROOM
Seriously.
Good to see you, guys.
Have one.
I don't smoke. Thanks.
Hi.
Writing notes?
-Let's eat after this.
-Okay.
Get up.
Same old rules. Long story short.
Last night,
there was a major burglary
at the Dongshan Mine.
Valuable items
and important materials were lost.
My higher-ups were on my neck all night.
From now on,
whoever doesn't have important tasks
will join the Special Task Force.
Tan. Give out the materials.
-Big cases? Ours?
-You in?
Captain.
Of course, we should
prioritize the big case.
Captain Feng.
Fangxu.
You already got ideas?
Tell us about it.
Everyone here will get to hear
the ideas of a PPSUC graduate.
Captain Feng.
The missing persons case
I'm working on is also quite urgent.
Seriously?
Yuanhang.
Has the case in Yuanlongli been filed?
Not yet.
How long have you been on this?
Four days.
They've been investigating
around the clock,
as busy as bees, 24 hours non-stop.
Yuanhang.
It's been four days.
We can't file a case
without finding the person.
But based on what we know,
this case is highly likely
to develop into a murder.
What makes you think
it's going to be a murder?
Is that based on proof or your intuition?
Captain Feng.
On probability.
Approximately 25% of missing persons cases
are ultimately classified as homicides.
For every four missing people,
one dies of unnatural causes.
And now we've passed the golden 72 hours
for finding the missing person.
Every extra day means more danger
to the missing person.
That's all.
Captain, this kid is a bookworm.
Please don't mind him.
You think I don't know that?
I was also annoyingly stubborn
when I was young.
This kid is persistent.
He'll make a good officer.
But then again,
you are also to blame
for his stubbornness.
You've been mentoring him for days.
Is this how you train him?
How can I mentor a college graduate?
Besides, you never said
that I'd be his mentor.
Isn't he sure that it's going
to turn into a murder?
How about this? Keep an eye on your area.
Transfer Ran Fangxu
to the Special Task Force.
Transfer him here to keep defying you?
Also, we're not allowed
to work cases alone.
How about this, Captain?
Give us an official order and a deadline.
This way, he'll have no complaints. Okay?
To be honest, I believe
that a missing person matters more
than some lost items.
Fine. How many days do you need?
Three days.
After three days, I'll bring that kid
to the Special Task Force.
Captain.
When are you going back
to the police station?
Also in three days.
Sneaky fox.
I…
There's nothing in it for me.
I did it all for you.
Thank you, Officer He.
For what?
You should thank Captain Feng.
He values talent.
Also, stop addressing me so formally.
What should I call you?
Our partnership will end soon.
I won't take advantage of you
and make you call me "sir".
Just call me He.
He.
I will do my best
to avoid delaying your return.
To be honest,
I have some selfish intentions.
This case has almost become a joke.
I can't go back empty-handed.
That's enough. Dig in. Dig in.
Clean it up afterward.
You like coriander too?
Have this. I'll have this.
It's a bit too much.
The case of Dongshan Mine
is the real deal.
But you're only interested
in a minor case.
My parents also went missing.
At first, they said it was nothing.
But later, they found…
their bodies.
We have three days. We have time.
Okay.
Wait.
MUSE FOOT MASSAGE, OWNER: ZHAO HONGMEI
How did I forget about her?
MUSE FOOT MASSAGE
So annoying.
Don't slam the door.
We have zero customers
after the police visited.
Not even a fly flew in.
It's all because of Mengmeng.
Listen.
No one is allowed
to mention Mengmeng again.
Do not gossip about her to anyone.
You hear me?
Yeah.
Lili. Get a perm.
Look at your hair.
It's like a pot of plants.
Ms. Zhao.
I need money for that.
You haven't paid me this month.
Why are you staring at me?
Do I have money on my face?
Still staring? Go get a perm.
QINGSONG CEMENT CONNECTS YOU AND ME
MUSE FOOT MASSAGE
I don't know Mengmeng so well.
I don't know what exactly happened to her.
What happened?
If I remember correctly,
you wanted to say something that night.
No one picked her.
She didn't earn anything,
so she stopped coming.
Why did she miss work?
I don't know.
Officer, stop pushing me.
I… I really don't know.
I have things to do. Can I leave now?
No.
Did Zhao Hongmei threaten you?
I can arrest her
if she's hiding something.
Rest assured. The information
you provide will be kept confidential.
-We're just trying to find Mengmeng.
-Yeah.
Actually, Mengmeng had some bad luck
right before she disappeared.
Bad luck?
Speaking of which,
she took the hit for me.
MUSE FOOT MASSAGE
Mr. Song.
You finally came to inspect our work.
Be careful.
Our young ladies have missed you so much.
Wait.
Briefcase.
Hurry.
MUSE FOOT MASSAGE
Welcome, Mr. Song.
-Mei.
-Yes?
I've traveled everywhere.
This is the best place for me.
Wherever you say is nice,
that's the nicest place.
Don't just stand there.
Hurry up and get around.
Get closer to Mr. Song.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Mr. Song. Lili. Get him in.
How dare you snatch my things?
I'll break your other leg, too.
Who are you?
Mr. Song, I'm Lili.
QINGSONG CEMENT
Who said you could touch my briefcase?
The essential oil might drip on it.
I paid for that.
Who said you could touch my briefcase?
How dare you touch my briefcase?
-How dare you!
-Mr. Song.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Go away. Go away.
Why are you angry with that dumb girl?
Don't be mad. I'll get you someone else.
Mengmeng.
Mengmeng is very sweet.
She'll make you happy.
Mengmeng. Hurry.
Come on. Mr. Song, this is Mengmeng.
Serve him well.
That briefcase says "Qingsong Cement".
-So Mr. Song is…
-Song Qingsong.
There is only one Mr. Song in Weiyang.
Hundreds of people gathered for a fight
outside the cement factory a few days ago.
It was because of him
and Cripple Du of the steel factory.
Those two are known to be enemies.
SONG QINGSONG
Song Qingsong met Xu Meng.
What happened next?
I thought Mr. Song could calm down
after he saw Mengmeng.
But Mengmeng started screaming in there.
And Mr. Song hit her even harder.
Why?
I think it was still
because of that briefcase.
-How dare you!
-Mr. Song, spare me.
Mr. Song, spare me.
Shut up.
-Still won't admit it?
-I am sorry.
Spare me.
I can make you disappear from Weiyang.
You hear me?
I can make you disappear.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Spare me.
-Still crying?
-Spare me.
Spare me.
Still crying, huh?
I can make you disappear!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Spare me.
-Still crying?
-Spare me.
Mr. Song kept beating her in that room.
Eventually, she went silent.
Song Qingsong said he'd made
Xu Meng disappear from Weiyang?
Yeah.
He kept repeating those words.
I heard him clearly.
Any idea what's in that briefcase?
White papers. A thick stack.
It hurt so much when he hit me with those.
Papers? Not money?
Not money.
Maybe for rich people,
paper is money,
and money sometimes is just paper.
They say, "Life is as fragile as paper."
People like us
are worth less than some papers.
Did Song Qingsong and Xu Meng
know each other?
Mengmeng and I used to work in Pattia.
Mr. Song often came
and asked for Mengmeng.
He wanted to keep her as his mistress.
But she turned him down.
That's why she got beaten
and sent to the hospital.
Didn't your boss do anything about it?
She dared not.
Mr. Song rented her the place.
What could she do?
The 18th floor of New York Block
is Song Qingsong's property?
He also owns the dorms downstairs.
Did Xu Meng tell you
why she turned him down?
She just didn't want to be a mistress.
Ms. Zhao said
that Mengmeng owed a lot of money.
QINGSONG CEMENT CONNECTS YOU AND ME
I just got back from a business trip.
Mr. Liu.
What I have at hand
is absolutely reliable.
I'll show you when the time is right.
But right now, I'm a bit short of funds.
If you're willing to help,
you can wait
to make loads of money with me.
Get back to me.
MISSING PERSON
MUSE
"Disappeared from Weiyang."
Doesn't that sound familiar?
You're talking about the guy
in the video rental shop?
That guy was drunk. It doesn't count.
Song Qingsong has plenty of women.
Why would he be so serious
about a massage lady?
Besides, Wolfie only killed chickens.
Even if Song Qingsong hired Wolfie,
the murder didn't happen.
What if he hired someone else?
Both Xu Meng and Lili were beaten
because they touched his briefcase.
Why was only Xu Meng threatened?
And the briefcase.
Song Qingsong didn't even trust his driver
and carried it with him
to the massage place.
What was in that briefcase?
A business owner usually carries
important documents,
checks, and bank drafts.
He.
Why does it sound like you're trying
to defend Song Qingsong?
Really?
Why?
Song Qingsong and Cripple Du take turns
to be the richest man in Weiyang.
They pay huge amounts of tax.
Even the authorities
have to show them some respect.
You know what I mean?
What does it have to do with the case?
We lack proof to tie them to this case.
That's why we can't act rashly
towards Song Qingsong.
I see.
Good.
You're afraid of Song Qingsong.
I'm afraid of Song Qingsong?
I'm a police officer.
Why would I be afraid?
We fight the bad people
and protect the good.
We're not sure that Song Qingsong
is a bad guy, right?
He put a woman in the hospital.
How is he a good guy?
Song Qingsong is known
to be a sneaky fox in Weiyang.
We can't just approach him
with Lili's testimony.
We may alert him.
We must form a strategy.
Like what?
Well… the strategy
is to not scare off the target,
but also not come away with nothing.
So…
I need to call someone.
Then I'll tell you more
about the strategy.
Don't be impulsive.
What are you doing?
Didn't you say that we lack proof?
I'll look for evidence at Yuanlongli now.
Why do you keep going to Yuanlongli?
You have a girlfriend there?
WEIYANG QINGSONG CEMENT FACTORY
Come here.
Brother-in-law.
Come closer.
I paid you to deal with someone.
This is how you handled it?
I can explain, brother-in-law.
Come here.
I've told you so many times.
What do you call me in the factory?
Mr. Song. Mr. Song.
I made that woman disappear
as you told me to.
I hired a hitman.
She and her dad. Both gone.
Only 40,000 yuan.
I told you to do it in person,
but you subcontracted it.
For kickbacks?
No. Absolutely not. I swear.
I dare not steal a penny from you.
Look at me.
Okay.
Is that woman really dead?
Yeah.
I looked into that hitman
before I hired him.
He's killed several people.
He's professional.
You saw it happening?
Yeah. I saw it happening.
Buried in the mountains.
Buried in the mountains?
Why don't I believe it?
Stupid woman.
Writing to blackmail me?
Go. Dig up the body.
If she's really dead, bring me her body.
Alright. Got it.
If she is still alive,
you will disappear from Weiyang.
PUBLIC TELEPHONE
WEIYANG QINGSONG CEMENT FACTORY
-Hello.
-What's up?
Song Qingsong is back?
Right.
Did you get the thing?
I'm not in the mood for this.
I don't care if you're in the mood.
Just tell me if you got it.
Will you shut up?
Are you all trying to drive me crazy?
Wu Shanlong. We're in the same boat.
If you don't get the thing,
the boat could flip anytime.
I got it. Exactly the same.
It's in the safe in my house now.
It's safe there. Happy now?
Ma'am. Any instructions?
My mom is not feeling well today.
She can't cook.
Huh? Is she okay?
Should I take her
to the hospital after work?
Waiting for you
is like waiting for pigs to fly.
I'm assigned to a business trip.
Pick up Xiaohe from my mom's place.
When will you be back?
Should I ask my mom
to keep Xiaohe for a few days?
Last time she was there,
she chased mice and fell into the pigsty.
The countryside is not safe.
And what if there are abductors?
Well, I'll take Xiaohe to our station.
That's the safest place.
Don't let her eat ice cream
and drink Coke when I'm away.
I wouldn't do that.
I don't even drink Coke myself.
Fine.
Countryside. What's wrong with it?
Get me another Coke.
Help yourself.
Kiddo.
Do you want to go out to work the case?
I've worked hard
and made contributions
on the Yuanlongli case.
I can tell Zhao Jie to hand this case
over to you tomorrow.
What do you think?
Tell me.
How can they put someone
so talented as you on the bench?
Right?
Your dad is experienced.
Plus your Uncle Ran.
The three of us will join forces
and crack this case in no time.
Dad. Let me emphasize it again.
Stay out of the Yuanlongli case.
And stop going to Yuanlongli.
Never again.
Why are you so worked up?
Who is it?
Ran.
Sir. How's the injury?
It's minor. Don't worry. Come in.
Kiddo. Look who's here.
This kid is so rude.
Your Uncle Ran is here.
Also, aren't you going to eat?
Acting up again?
Maybe work is stressful these days.
Oh, right. Where were you?
Why did you vanish when the police came?
I'm just a teacher.
I shouldn't cause them trouble.
Why would you say that?
By order of seniority,
you're their senior.
Come on. Let's talk in my room.
Come to my room.
-Sir.
-Yes?
All these things are about Yuanlongli?
Yeah.
These are my treasures.
And yours.
NOTEBOOK
How…
You walked away without a care
and left them there.
They naturally became mine.
Actually,
I've always had a feeling.
I've always felt that the missing people
in Yuanlongli in the past few years…
SONG QINGSONG
…were related to Xu Meng
and her father's case 18 years ago.
You saw it today.
A kid hid in Yuanlongli
and attacked whoever he saw.
Isn't it weird?
Shouldn't we look into Yuanlongli?
Sir, we found the kid.
Just leave it to the police.
We're not qualified to intervene.
Yeah. We're not qualified.
You left. I retired.
But this is Xiaohe's first case,
after all.
Xiaohe's case?
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Zhao Jie just announced it this evening.
Xiaohe is still young.
This is her first case.
She doesn't catch on
as fast as you did back then.
This kid is way too stubborn.
She clearly needs help,
but just doesn't say it.
Ran.
I genuinely hope
that the two of us can join hands again
to help Xiaohe.
Rest assured. I promise
I will do my best
to avoid delaying your return.
Okay?
Then it's settled.
Let me thank you on behalf of Xiaohe.
YUANLONGLI INTERNATIONAL GARDEN
Officer Ran.
Why are you here?
These are for you.
Why did you buy new ones? No need.
It's the least I could do.
I have to thank you.
Here.
Still, you didn't have
to come all the way here.
Come in and have some water.
No need. I have things to do.
Still that thing upstairs?
People have been terrified.
You haven't found her?
Officer Ran.
Wang Xinglong said you came
to the fourth floor.
Wait for me. Be right there.
Okay.
Right. How's the injury?
It's basically healed.
It won't leave a scar.
Go ahead. Business first.
Tell me if you need help.
Thanks.
Then…
CASUAL SNEAKERS
Officer Ran.
Do you know the deal
with that woman in 415?
-What about her?
-She was being kept as a mistress.
True.
The one who kept her was an old man.
In his seventies.
Last winter, the old man slipped
on the stairs and fell.
Cerebral hemorrhage. He died.
That apartment she lives in
belonged to that old man.
But it seems that he never gave it
to that woman.
Why did she do that? She's so pretty.
She could have married any decent guy.
Why did she pick an old man?
Officer Ran. We're here.
After Pattia was seized,
Mr. Song gave us the keys
to these two floors
and asked us to look for tenants.
This half belongs to merchants.
The left-hand side
used to be Pattia's dorm.
Which one should we check first?
QIHUANG CLINIC
Raid! Raid!
PRIVATE ROOM 3
That one.
Okay.
ANSWER
I DON'T BELIEVE DREAMS ARE FALSE
I DON'T BELIEVE DEATH HAS NO RETRIBUTION
IF THE SEA IS DESTINED TO BURST ITS DIKES
LET ALL THE BITTER WATERS
POUR INTO MY HEART
MENGMENG NO.23
It's their work badge in Pattia.
This is Mengmeng. Do you know her?
The missing ghost?
A suspected missing person.
I can't tell.
There are 20 or 30 young ladies
coming and going here,
all heavily made up.
I don't recognize her without makeup.
It's also a dorm next door.
Someone is still living here?
Worker of Pattia.
In the front. Where is she?
Where did she go?
Don't throw my cards away.
Where is the gaming machine? Take it out.
Do you hear me? I'm counting to three.
One. Two.
Hey!
How come it's you?
You scared me to death.
This kid plays games all day.
He's ruined.
-Thanks.
-I forbid him to play.
Well, he hid in the corridor
and kept playing.
What are you wearing?
Women's clothes?
You think I'll go easy on you?
Ma'am, calm down.
He's just a kid.
-Unbelievable.
-Ma'am.
These…
Playing games all day long.
It's summer vacation. So I'm playing.
-What's the big deal?
-"What's the big deal"?
Ma'am, I'm here to learn
about the missing person.
They say this floor
was Pattia's staff dorm before.
Pattia was seized before I moved here.
Have you seen anything weird
in the building recently?
The two next door moved out last month.
Business was bad.
The one across, 1703, is a residence.
We only hear men and women
crying and shouting
in the middle of the night.
It's so…
You know?
So, 1703 is not a store?
Officer Ran. I forgot.
Room 1703 is the biggest.
Mr. Song keeps it for himself.
They say Mr. Song
keeps his mistress in 1703.
Shush!
Ma'am, have you seen him
bringing anyone?
But often, some flashy-dressed women
come to get clothes altered.
Guess what.
The thing is, it's never
the same person twice.
Ma'am, have you seen this woman?
How can I remember?
I do my best to avoid them. What bad luck.
Don't you want to ask about 1703?
Mr. Song is home.
Song Qingsong is home?
Yeah.
That door squeaks whenever it opens.
I would know if he comes out.
What is this?
Mr. Song.
Are you home? I'm the property manager.
Hello.
Police, Nanshan Branch.
I have some questions.
I know you're home. Please open the door.
Mr. Song.
Are you Song Qingsong?
No. I'm Mr. Song's secretary.
I came to get some papers.
What can I do for you?
-Let me take a look.
-I'm afraid I can't.
This is not my place.
I don't have a say here.
When is he coming back?
Well… I'm not sure.
He usually gets drunk at night
and sleeps here.
Officer, he's in a hurry for these files.
If you've got nothing else,
please head back.
It's too hot. Can I have some water?
The water is out.
-Coke is fine, too.
-Coke is for me.
Shit!
This guy is a burglar.
Ouch. Ma Qiang. Push.
-Lock the door.
-Okay.
Go.
Dad. What's the next move
of the horse stance side strike?
Kick. Throat lock.
Teach me again.
You're biting off more than you can chew.
GOLDEN ROCK AUDIO SHOP OPENING
The rock singers all look weird.
Rocking and rolling.
How can they look good?
What a heavy bag for a third grader.
The teachers and parents
are oppressing children.
Dad. Are we going to Grandma's?
Do you like Grandma's place, kiddo?
Yeah, of course.
She has Hua and Huang.
We can catch mice in the yard.
Then let's go to Grandma's.
-Dad, you're the best.
-Get in.
Got a lead. Return to the unit. Ran.
Xiaohe. We won't go to Grandma's yet.
Dad. You're going back on your word again.
Want to see where Dad works?
The police station?
Are there a lot of bad people
locked up there?
Are you afraid?
Not at all. My dad catches bad guys.
Alright, sit tight.
Slow down. What's the rush?
Officer Zhang. Officer Li.
You clown.
You're kind of a regular here.
Can't bear to leave, huh?
-Thanks. You helped us a lot.
-No problem.
I'd like to borrow the loot.
Huh?
Dad. What did he do?
Officer He. Long time no see.
Keep your mouth shut.
Just saying hi.
He's a pickpocket.
I've caught him before.
Does he really pick pockets?
Xiaohe. Say hi to Uncle Ran.
Hello, Xiaohe.
You're Uncle Ran, the graduate from PPSUC?
You're pretty well-informed.
My mom told my dad to learn from you.
Don't talk nonsense.
How am I talking nonsense?
My mom also said
that you should butter up Uncle Ran
so he can promote you
once he becomes an official.
Finished your summer break homework?
Xiaohe. Uncle Ran and I
have things to talk about.
Go to the office. Finish your homework.
No. I’m going to play
basketball in the yard.
Hey you!
Uncle Ran. Come play when you're done.
What a kid…
Right, He. Song Qingsong…
I've figured out what to do about him.
Let's wait for him outside
the cement factory.
-Once he comes out…
-No.
He will be here soon.
Huh?